Guide to the Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group files, 1988-2008.
Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group files
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group files, 1988-2008.
53-16-3705
Cornell Theory Center.Visualization Group.
3 hard drives (500 GB), 1.5 cubic foot.
Movie Film
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains digital files, created by Chris Pelkie, of videotapes and DVDs from the Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Clients of the Visualization Group were researchers (faculty, grad students, some undergrads, some corporate) of the Cornell Theory Center or CNSF (Cornell National Supercomputer Facility). Copyright notices, when present, usually attribute copyright to Cornell University. Copies were almost certainly given to the principal investigators in every case; other copies may have been distributed to other interested parties. The group ceased operations in 2008.
Chris Pelkie was the Scientific Visualization Producer for the group.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains digital files, created by Chris Pelkie, of videotapes and DVDs from the Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group. The earliest tape is probably from 1988, and the most recent visualization movies (not necessarily tape) are from 2008. For the most part, these are scientific visualizations, i.e., graphics produced from numeric data. Most represent either/or time series or motion sequence (rotation, for example) of the visualized phenomena. There are a few live action videos, shot of the visualization studio or at trade shows or workshops, etc. Some of the more highly produced videos include narration and/or music beds. Many are silent. Most have titles/credits/attributions.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Theory Center.; Cornell Theory Center.Visualization Group.
Subjects:
Computer graphics.; Visualization.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Videos
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1988-1990; DVD-223 (Box 1)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1991; DVD-224 (Box 1)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1992; DVD-225 (Box 1)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1992-1993; DVD-226 (Box 1)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1993; DVD-227 (Box 1)
  - Assorted Wayne Lytle CTC Projects (2c.), 1988-1997; DVD-228 (Box 2)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Demo Reels (2c.), 1988-1990; DVD-229 (Box 2)
  - Evelyn (Evi) Goldfield Projects DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1989-1993; DVD-230 (Box 2)
  - Dynamical Simulation of Curved Grain Boundaries Composed of Pyramidal-Shaped Ledges Re-Jehn Jahn & Paul Bristowe, MIT; Wayne Lytle, CNSF DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1989, 2006; DVD-231 (Box 2)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Jupiter, Wayne Lytle DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1989; DVD-232 (Box 2)
  - Cornell National Supercomputer Facility Neptune, Wayne Lytle DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1989; DVD-233 (Box 2)
  - Visualization of Simulated Treatment of an Ocular Tumor; Wayne Lytle, et al; Mark Rondeau, et al DVD-ROM (Uncompr 10-bit MOV, non-scrolling titles) (2c.), 1989, 2005; DVD-234 (Box 2)
  - Visualization of Simulated Treatment of an Ocular Tumor; Wayne Lytle, et al; Mark Rondeau, et al DVD-ROM (MOV and WMV) (3c.), 1989, 2005; DVD-235 (Box 2)
  - Sidney Leibovich Projects CNSF/CTC; A. Tandon, G. Yang, R. Bhaskaran, T. Haeusser; DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1989-2000; DVD-236 (Box 2)
  - Laser Effects on Molecular Dynamics in Optically Active Media; Myron Evans, Chris Pelkie [Pt.1] DVD-NTSC, 1990; DVD-237 (Box 2)
  - Simulation of Molecualr Dynamics on the Loosely Coupled Array of Processors; M. W. Evans, G. C. Lie, E. Clementi [Pt.2] DVD-NTSC, 1987; DVD-237 (Box 2)
  - Thomas M. Bartol Jr. CNSF/CTC Projects DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM, 1990-1991; DVD-238 (Box 2)
  - Ab Initio Electronic Structure of Quartz; Michael Teter & Douglas Allan; C.U. & Corning, Inc. DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1990; DVD-239 (Box 2)
  - Shape Distributions of Linear and Circular Macromolecules; Gaoyuan Wei and B. E. Eichinger, University of Washington DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1990; DVD-240 (Box 2)
  - An Anisotropic Convection Model for the Upper Mantle; Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson (Cornell); Kristin Bennett, H-R Wenk (UC Berkeley) DVD-ROM 1, 1991; DVD-241 (Box 2)
  - An Anisotropic Convection Model for the Upper Mantle; Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson (Cornell); Kristin Bennett, H-R Wenk (UC Berkeley) DVD-ROM 2, 1991; DVD-242 (Box 2)
  - An Anisotropic Convection Model for the Upper Mantle; Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson (Cornell); Kristin Bennett, H-R Wenk (UC Berkeley), 1991; DVD-243 (Box 2)
  - Cyrus Aidun Projects DVD/DVD-ROM, 1991; DVD-244 (Box 2)
  - Yvan Chastel Disk 1, 1991; DVD-245 (Box 2)
  - Yvan Chastel Disk 2, 1991; DVD-246 (Box 2)
  - Simulation of the Structure of Amorphous Silicon Dioxide with Long-Range Interaction; John Rittner - Shafiqur Rahman, Allegheny College DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1991; DVD-247 (Box 2)
  - Optimization of Groundwater Remediation with Time-varying Pumping Rates; Christine Shoemaker, Gregory Whiffen, Liang-Cheng Chang DVD/DVD-ROM, 1991; DVD-248 (Box 2)
  - Optimization of Groundwater Remediation with Time-varying Pumping Rates; Christine Shoemaker, et al DVD-ROM, 1991; DVD-249 (Box 2)
  - Aerobic Bioremediation; Christine Shoemaker, et al DVD-ROM, 1995; DVD-249 (Box 2)
  - Dynamics of Phase Transitions in Nonlinear Viscoelasticity; Pieter Swart - Phillip Holmes DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1991; DVD-250 (Box 2)
  - Tropical Storm Delia; Rudy Slingerland and Tim Keen, Pennsylvania State University DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1991; DVD-251 (Box 2)
  - Does This Pulsar Have Orbiting Planets?; Wayne Lytle, et al DVD-ROM 1, 1992; DVD-252 (Box 2)
  - Does This Pulsar Have Orbiting Planets?; Wayne Lytle, et al DVD-ROM 2, 1992; DVD-253 (Box 2)
  - 1. Does This Pulsar Have Orbiting Planets?; 2. Discovery of Planets; Wayne Lytle, et al DVD-NTSC, 1992; DVD-254 (Box 2)
  - 1. Does This Pulsar Have Orbiting Planets?; 2. Discovery of Planets; Wayne Lytle, et al DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1992; DVD-254a (Box 2)
  - Misc Space Sciences projects; Bill Bottke, Daniel Coe, Elaina McCarty, Dave Hysell, Jean-Luc Margot, Dmitry Meyerson, Sayas Shume DVD-R, 1992-2004; DVD-255 (Box 3)
  - Misc Space Sciences projects; Bill Bottke, Daniel Coe, Elaina McCarty, Dave Hysell, Jean-Luc Margot, Dmitry Meyerson, Sayas Shume DVD/DVD-ROM, 1992-2004; DVD-256 (Box 3)
  - Three-Dimensional Acoustic Visualization of Zooplankton Patchiness on Georges Bank; Charles Greene, 1992-2003; DVD-257 (Box 3)
  - Three-Dimensional Acoustic Visualization of Zooplankton Patchiness on Georges Bank; Charles Greene, 1992-2003; DVD-258 (Box 3)
  - Charles Greene Video projects DVD-Video/ DVD-ROM (2c.), 1992-1998; DVD-259 (Box 3)
  - Use of Polycrystal Plasticity to Simulate Texture Evolution During Cold Rolling of Fe-3%Si; Gorti Sarma, Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson DVD-ROM 1, 1993, 1994; DVD-260 (Box 3)
  - Use of Polycrystal Plasticity to Simulate Texture Evolution During Cold Rolling of Fe-3%Si; Gorti Sarma, Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson DVD-ROM 2, 1993, 1994; DVD-261 (Box 3)
  - Use of Polycrystal Plasticity to Simulate Texture Evolution During Cold Rolling of Fe-3%Si; Gorti Sarma, Yvan Chastel, Paul Dawson DVD-NTSC, 1993, 1994; DVD-262 (Box 3)
  - 1st 10 days of May 1993 (time step 19): Visualization of Time Series Vegetation Indices of the Guinea Savannah Woodland, Ghana, West Africa; Stephen D. DeGloria and Marybeth Bleecker Vargha DVD/DVD-ROM, 1993; DVD-263 (Box 3)
  - Larry Brown, Bryan Isacks, Eric Fielding; Bhutan/Tibet DVD/DVD-ROM, 1993; DVD-264 (Box 3)
  - Brown/Fielding, Bhutan/Tibet, 1993, 1995; DVD-265 (Box 3)
  - Dawson Alexei/Gorti, 1993; DVD-266 (Box 3)
  - Monte Carlo Simulation of Charged Particles under Electric Fields; Chris Pelkie, Bruce land, Jyun-Hwei Tsai, Pao-Tzung Lai, Chuan-Chang Wang DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1993; DVD-267 (Box 3)
  - A Tour of the Cornell Theory Center DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1993; DVD-268 (Box 3)
  - CTC Tour B-Roll 1 of 2 DVD-ROM, 1993; DVD-269 (Box 3)
  - CTC Tour B-Roll 2 of 2 DVD-ROM, 1993; DVD-270 (Box 3)
  - Paul Dawson DVD-ROM, 1994-2004; DVD-271 (Box 3)
  - Dawson Property Browser DVD-ROM, 1994; DVD-272 (Box 3)
  - See: Box 7, CD-357, DVD-273 (Box 3)
  - Sensorless Manipulation using Transverse Vibrations of a Plate; Vivek Bhatt, Karl Bohringer, Kenneth Goldberg; DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1995; DVD-274 (Box 3)
  - Mapping and Visualizing Biodiversity in New York State: Visualization of Diffusely Distributed Pollutants using Spatially-explicit Landscape Models; Stephen D. DeGloria, Dennis Swaney, Chris Pelkie, Fuan Tsai, Wen-Ling Kuo, Charles E. McCulloch DVD, 1995; DVD-275 (Box 3)
  - Mapping and Visualizing Biodiversity in New York State: GAP; Stephen D. DeGloria, Charles Smith DVD-ROM 1, 1995; DVD-276 (Box 3)
  - Mapping and Visualizing Biodiversity in New York State: GAP; Stephen D. DeGloria, Charles Smith DVD-ROM 2, 1995; DVD-277 (Box 3)
  - Mapping and Visualizing Biodiversity in New York State: GAP; Stephen D. DeGloria, Charles Smith (.sit) DVD-ROM 2, 1995; DVD-277a (Box 3)
  - Mapping and Visualizing Biodiversity in New York State: GAP; Stephen D. DeGloria, Charles Smith DVD, 1995; DVD-278 (Box 3)
  - Visualization of Diffusely Distributed Pollutants Using Spatially -explicit Landscape Models; Stephen D. DeGloria, Dennis Swaney, Chris Pelkie, Fuan Tsai, Wen-Ling Kuo, Charles E. McCulloch DVD-ROM, 1996; DVD-279 (Box 3)
  - Visualization of Diffusely Distributed Pollutants Using Spatially -explicit Landscape Models: AEP; Stephen D. DeGloria et al DVD-ROM 1, 1996; DVD-280 (Box 3)
  - Visualization of Diffusely Distributed Pollutants Using Spatially -explicit Landscape Models: AEP; Stephen D. DeGloria et al DVD-ROM 2, 1996; DVD-281 (Box 3)
  - Bhutan Flight; Brown/Fielding DVD, 1995; DVD-282 (Box 3)
  - Computational Enzymology: Simulation of the Reaction in Malate Dehydrogenase; Bash, Ho, Gillilan DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1996, 1997; DVD-283 (Box 3)
  - Todd Cowen DVD, 1996; DVD-284 (Box 3)
  - CTC Workshops 1996-2005 DVD-ROM, 1996; DVD-285 (Box 3)
  - NYS GIS DVD, 1997; DVD-286 (Box 3)
  - Todd Cowen DVD-R, 1998-2000; DVD-287 (Box 3)
  - Rick Durrett DVD-ROM, 1998-1999; DVD-288 (Box 4)
  - Rick Durrett DVD-R, 1998-1999; DVD-289 (Box 4)
  - Philip Liu DVD, 1998; DVD-290 (Box 4)
  - Philip Liu DVD, 1998; DVD-291 (Box 4)
  - Philip Liu DVD, 1998; DVD-292 (Box 4)
  - Philip Liu DVD-R, 1998; DVD-293 (Box 4)
  - Intrinsic Nanoscale Localization on Antiferromagnetic Spin Lattices; Uli Schwarz, A. J. Sievers DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM (2c.), 1998; DVD-294 (Box 4)
  - Bill Bottke Projects DVD/DVD-ROM, 1999; DVD-295 (Box 4)
  - Iain Boyd DVD-R, 1999; DVD-296 (Box 4)
  - Margaret Corbit Projects DVD-ROM, 1999, 2004; DVD-297 (Box 4)
  - Andrew Folland DVD, 1999; DVD-298 (Box 4)
  - Andrew Folland DVD, 1999; DVD-299 (Box 4)
  - Raghu Govardhan, Williamson DVD, 1999-2000; DVD-300 (Box 4)
  - Vortex-Induced Vibration of a Cylinder; Raghu Govardhan, C. H. K.Williamson, C. Pelkie DVD-R, 1999-2000; DVD-301 (Box 4)
  - "2S" and "2P" Wake Vortex Modes, Vortex Formation Modes of a Freely Vibrating Cylinder; Raghu Govardhan, C. H. K. Williamson DVD-R, 1999-2003; DVD-302 (Box 4)
  - Charles Williamson DVD-ROM, 1999-2004; DVD-303 (Box 4)
  - SC (SciCentr) 00 Booth Videos: Steve Lantz, John Zollweg, Jarek Meller, Lucy Walle DVD-ROM, 2000; DVD-304 (Box 4)
  - Dawson Web Movies DVD 1, 2000; DVD-305 (Box 4)
  - Dawson Web Movies DVD 2, 2000; DVD-306 (Box 4)
  - Dawson Web Movies DVD 3, 2000; DVD-307 (Box 4)
  - Leibovich, Bhaskaran DVD, 2000; DVD-308 (Box 4)
  - Michel Louge, Nasa Pellets DVD, 2000; DVD-309 (Box 4)
  - Montemagno, Peters DVD 1, 2000; DVD-310 (Box 4)
  - Montemagno, Peters DVD 2, 2000; DVD-311 (Box 4)
  - Montemagno, Peters DVD 3, 2000; DVD-312 (Box 4)
  - Montemagno, Peters DVD 4, 2000; DVD-313 (Box 4)
  - Montemagno, Peters DVD 5, 2000; DVD-314 (Box 4)
  - Todd Cowen, Stawar Vioco DVD, 2000; DVD-315 (Box 4)
  - Sc 00; Meller, Lantz DVD, 2000; DVD-316 (Box 4)
  - SC 00 ISAA VW; Lantz DVD, 2000-2001; DVD-317 (Box 4)
  - Reeves DVD, 2000; DVD-318 (Box 4)
  - Talking Head; Lucy Walle DVD, 2000; DVD-319 (Box 4)
  - SC 00 Multi Matlab; Movie John Zollweg DVD 1, 2000; DVD-320 (Box 4)
  - SC 00 Multi Matlab; John Zollweg DVD 2, 2000; DVD-321 (Box 4)
  - Tonal Recognition; Carol Krumhansl, Petri Toiviainen DVD, 2000; DVD-322 (Box 4)
  - Michel Louge, Rolf Verberg DVD-ROM (2c.), 2000-2004; DVD-323 (Box 4)
  - Integrating Life Processes into Nanofabricated Devices; Carol Montemagno, Francis Peters DVD-ROM 1, 2000; DVD-324 (Box 4)
  - Integrating Life Processes into Nanofabricated Devices; Carol Montemagno, Francis Peters DVD-ROM 2, 2000; DVD-325 (Box 4)
  - Integrating Life Processes into Nanofabricated Devices; Carol Montemagno, Francis Peters DVD-ROM, 2000; DVD-326 (Box 4)
  - Integrating Life Processes into Nanofabricated Devices; Carol Montemagno, Francis Peters DVD-ROM, 2000; DVD-327 (Box 4)
  - Lung Tumor Visualization; Tony Reeves DVD/DVD-ROM, 2000; DVD-328 (Box 4)
  - CTC Finance Projects; Coleman, Protter, Lee, Mansfield DVD-ROM (2c.), 2001-2002; DVD-329 (Box 4)
  - CTC-Manhattan; Peter Mansfield DVD/DVD-ROM 1, 2001; DVD-330 (Box 4)
  - CTC-Manhattan; Peter Mansfield DVD/DVD-ROM 2, 2001; DVD-331 (Box 4)
  - Animation Data; Felix Flemming, Williamson DVD, 2001; DVD-332 (Box 4)
  - DX/Data; Felix Flemming, Williamson, Nathan Jauvtis DVD 1, 2001; DVD-333 (Box 4)
  - Felix Flemming, Williamson, Nathan Jauvtis DVD 2, 2001; DVD-334 (Box 4)
  - Gerd Heber DVD 1, 2001; DVD-335 (Box 4)
  - Gerd Heber DVD 2, 2001; DVD-336 (Box 4)
  - Gerd Heber, 2001-2007; DVD-337 (Box 5)
  - Anthony Ingraffea, 1999-2007; DVD-337 (Box 5)
  - Peter Mansfield Projects DVD-R, 2001; DVD-338 (Box 5)
  - See: Box 7, CD-358, DVD-339 (Box 5)
  - Ciro Cerretelli, Williamson DVD, 2002; DVD-340 (Box 5)
  - The Physical Mechanism for Vortex Merging; Ciro Cerretelli DVD-R/DVD-ROM, 2002-2003; DVD-341 (Box 5)
  - VW Talk; Gerd Heber DVD-1, 2002-2003; DVD-342 (Box 5)
  - VW Talk; Gerd Heber DVD-2, 2002-2003; DVD-343 (Box 5)
  - VW Talk; Gerd Heber DVD-3, 2002-2003; DVD-344 (Box 5)
  - Electric Predators Project; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM 1, 2003; DVD-345a (Box 5)
  - Electric Predators Project; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM 2, 2003; DVD-345b (Box 5)
  - Electric Predators Project; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM 3, 2003; DVD-345c (Box 5)
  - Electric Predators of the Night; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM, 2003; DVD-346 (Box 5)
  - CTC SC 03 Archive DVD-ROM 1, 2003; DVD-347 (Box 5)
  - CTC SC 03 Archive DVD-ROM 2, 2003; DVD-348 (Box 5)
  - Polycrystal DVD/DVD-ROM, 2003, 2004; DVD-349 (Box 5)
  - Boxing Day '04 Tsunami Preliminary Visualization DVD, 2004; DVD-350 (Box 5)
  - Philip Liu Projects: Tsunami misc; Philip Liu, Wu Tso-Ren DVD, 2005; DVD-351 (Box 5)
  - Boxing Day '04 Tsunami Preliminary Visualization DVD-1, 2004; DVD-352 (Box 5)
  - Boxing Day '04 Tsunami Preliminary Visualization DVD-2, 2004; DVD-353 (Box 5)
  - Boxing Day '04 Tsunami Preliminary Visualization DVD-3, 2004; DVD-354 (Box 5)
  - Boxing Day '04 Tsunami Preliminary Visualization DVD-4, 2004; DVD-355 (Box 5)
  - CTC SciCentr: Cornell Theory Center SciCentr 2004 Promo DVD/DVD-ROM, 2004; DVD-356 (Box 5)
  - ActiveWorlds/Cornell Theory Center SciCentr 2004 Promo; Margaret Corbit DVD/DVD-ROM, 2004; DVD-357 (Box 5)
  - Structures and Haplotypes of Brassica Anti-Self-pollination Protein; Thanat Chookajorn DVD/DVD-ROM, 2004; DVD-358 (Box 5)
  - Heber Polycrystal 04 Archive; Gerd Heber DVD/DVD-ROM (2c.), 2004; DVD-359 (Box 5)
  - NCBI (National Center for Biotechnology Information) Lectures; Rana Morris, Eric Sayers DVD-1, 2004; DVD-360 (Box 5)
  - NCBI Lectures; Rana Morris, Eric Sayers DVD-2, 2004; DVD-361 (Box 5)
  - NCBI Lectures; Rana Morris, Eric Sayers DVD-3, 2004; DVD-362 (Box 5)
  - NCBI Lab, Andrei Gabrielian DVD 1, 2004; DVD-363 (Box 5)
  - NCBI Lab, Andrei Gabrielian DVD 2, 2004; DVD-364 (Box 5)
  - NCBI Lectures and Labs; Lecturers: Rana Morris, Eric Sayers; Lab Instructor: Andrei Gabrielian DVD 1, 2004; DVD-365 (Box 5)
  - Black Hole Visualizations: Naked Singularity, Toroidal Black Hole, Collisions of Black Holes DVD/DVD-ROM, 2004; DVD-366 (Box 5)
  - SC 04 Promo Archive DVD-ROM, 2004; DVD-367 (Box 6)
  - Ganesh Subramanian DVD, 2004-2005; DVD-368 (Box 6)
  - Black Hole Visualizations 2; Saul Teukolsky DVD/DVD-R, 2004; DVD-369 (Box 6)
  - Determining Strain Pole Figures from Diffraction Experiments; Dmitry Bershadsky DVD/DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-370 (Box 6)
  - Determining Strain Pole Figures from Diffraction Experiments; Dmitry Bershadsky DVD/DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-371 (Box 6)
  - Film Festival: Chisembe: Shadow Hunters of Malawi; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM 1, 2005; DVD-372 (Box 6)
  - Film Festival: Chisembe: Shadow Hunters of Malawi; Matt Arnegard DVD-ROM 2, 2005; DVD-373 (Box 6)
  - See: Box 7, CD-359, DVD-374 (Box 6)
  - Film Festival: Chisembe: Shadow Hunters of Malawi; Matt Arnegard DVD-NTSC, 2005; DVD-375 (Box 6)
  - CTC Misc. Projects DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-376 (Box 6)
  - CTC SciCentr SciFair DVD/DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-377 (Box 6)
  - CTC SciCentr SciFair DVD, 2005; DVD-378 (Box 6)
  - CTC 20th Visualization Review; CTC 20th Anniversary Review DVD/DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-379 (Box 6)
  - See: Box 5, DVD-345c, DVD-380 (Box 6)
  - Weill Talk; Chris Pelkie DVD-381 (2c.), 2005; DVD-381 (Box 6)
  - Lab of O[rnithology] Ivory-billed Woodpecker Specimen; Hurf Sheldon DVD-ROM 1, 2005; DVD-382 (Box 6)
  - Lab of O Ivory-billed Woodpecker Specimen; Hurf Sheldon DVD-ROM 2, 2005; DVD-383 (Box 6)
  - Xiaolong Yin, Don Koch DVD-ROM, 2005; DVD-384 (Box 6)
  - Ciro Cerretelli, Williamson DVD, 2006; DVD-385 (Box 6)
  - SciFair Promo DVD-ROM, 2006; DVD-386 (Box 6)
  - SciFair Promo DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM, 2006; DVD-387 (Box 6)
  - CTC Visualization Services, CAVE Virtual Reality, SciCentr DVD, 2006; DVD-388 (Box 6)
  - Artwork for CTC Promo DVD; DVD-R, 2006; DVD-389 (Box 6)
  - CTC Promo DVD; DVD, 2006; DVD-390 (Box 6)
  - CTC Promo DVD, CAVE Virtual Reality DVD-ROM 1, 2006; DVD-391 (Box 6)
  - CTC Promo DVD, CAVE Virtual Reality DVD-ROM 2, 2006; DVD-392 (Box 6)
  - CTC Promo DVD, CAVE Virtual Reality DVD-ROM 3, 2006; DVD-393 (Box 6)
  - CTC Promo DVD, VR Interview Outtakes; Henry Richardson, Hod Lipson, Lois Pollack DVD-ROM, 2006; DVD-394 (Box 6)
  - Electric Fish Animation Project; Laurieanne Dent, 2006-2007; DVD-395 (Box 6)
  - Project Files, Ray Fertig DVD, 2006; DVD-396 (Box 6)
  - Linear Supply Curves Project; Philip Protter DVD, 2006; DVD-397 (Box 6)
  - Nature Physics; Jim Sethna, 2007; DVD-398 (Box 6)
  - Projects; Chris Myers DVD, 2006-2007; DVD-398 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 1, 2007; DVD-399 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 2, 2007; DVD-400 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 3, 2007; DVD-401 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 4, 2007; DVD-402 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 5, 2007; DVD-403 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 6, 2007; DVD-404 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 7, 2007; DVD-405 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 8, 2007; DVD-406 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 9, 2007; DVD-407 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 10, 2007; DVD-408 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 11, 2007; DVD-409 (Box 6)
  - Extending Safe life: Predicting Microstructurally Small Cracks DVD-NTSC/DVD-ROM, 2007; DVD-410 (Box 6)
  - DARPATech BKP 12, 2007; DVD-411 (Box 7)
  - DARPATech BKP 13, 2007; DVD-412 (Box 7)
  - Fuchs, Kaplitt, Stieg DVD 1, 2007; DVD-413 (Box 7)
  - Fuchs, Stieg DVD 2, 2007; DVD-414 (Box 7)
  - Fuchs, Stieg, Kaplitt DVD 3, 2007; DVD-415 (Box 7)
  - CUSat 2007; Ian Livingston DVD, 2007; DVD-416 (Box 7)
  - Cover for 04/20/07 Journal of Biological Chemistry; Jocelyn Rose, et al DVD, 2007; DVD-417 (Box 7)
  - Prospective Cell cover project; Michelle Wang, et al DVD, 2007; DVD-418 (Box 7)
  - Extending Safe life: Predicting Microstructurally Small Cracks DVD-NTSC (see also DVD-410), no date; DVD-419 (Box 7)
  - Bottke Evolution DVD-1, no date; DVD-420 (Box 7)
  - Bottke Evolution DVD-2, no date; DVD-421 (Box 7)
  - Bottke Smear DVD-1, no date; DVD-422 (Box 7)
  - Bottke Smear DVD-2, no date; DVD-423 (Box 7)
  - Mansfield Head Anim DVD 1, no date; DVD-424 (Box 7)
  - Mansfield Project Media DVD 1, no date; DVD-425 (Box 7)
  - Mansfield Project Media DVD 2, no date; DVD-426 (Box 7)
  - Mansfield Project Media DVD 3, no date; DVD-427 (Box 7)
  - Mansfield Projects DVD, no date; DVD-428 (Box 7)
  - Chris Pelkie DARPATech Projects DVD, no date; DVD-429 (Box 7)
  - Wenk Mantle Work; Dawson Wenk DVD 1, no date; DVD-430 (Box 7)
  - Wenk Mantle Work; Dawson Wenk DVD 2, no date; DVD-431 (Box 7)
  - Wenk Mantle Work; Dawson Wenk DVD 3, no date; DVD-432 (Box 7)
  - Wenk Mantle Work; Dawson Wenk DVD 4, no date; DVD-433 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 1, no date; DVD-434 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 2, no date; DVD-435 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 3, no date; DVD-436 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 4, no date; DVD-437 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 5, no date; DVD-438 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria AEP DVD 6, no date; DVD-439 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria GAP DVD 1, no date; DVD-440 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria GAP DVD 2, no date; DVD-441 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria GAP DVD 3, no date; DVD-442 (Box 7)
  - DeGloria GAP DVD 4, no date; DVD-443 (Box 7)
  - Media 100; Rick Durrett DVD 1, no date; DVD-444 (Box 7)
  - Media 100; Rick Durrett DVD 2, no date; DVD-445 (Box 7)
  - Media 100; Rick Durrett DVD 3, no date; DVD-446 (Box 7)
  - Media 100; Rick Durrett DVD 4, no date; DVD-447 (Box 7)
  - Misc. CTC (Pelkie) DVD 1, no date; DVD-448 (Box 7)
  - Misc. CTC (Pelkie) DVD 2, no date; DVD-449 (Box 7)
  - Beaudoin, Kessler, Jospe Music CD, 1994; CD-357 (Box 7)
  - Phil Protter S&P CD-ROM, 2001; CD-358 (Box 7)
  - Film Festival: Chisembe: Shadow Hunters of Malawi; Fish Electric Field Sketches; Matt Arnegard CD-ROM, 2005; CD-359 (Box 7)
  - Promo DVD 1 0603, 2003; V-1367 (Box 9)
  - Promo DVD 2 0603, 2003; V-1368 (Box 9)
  - Promo DVD 3 0603, 2003; V-1369 (Box 9)
  - Dawson 5-D viewer NIV Covar Matrix, V-1370 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber DARPATECH demo DVD 06-13-07, 2007; V-1371 (Box 9)
  - Drew Dolgert "Porting" Virtual Workshop 1, 2004; V-1372 (Box 9)
  - Drew Dolgert "Porting" Virtual Workshop 2, 2004; V-1373 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg 1, [1993]; V-1374 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg 2, 1993; V-1375 (Box 9)
  - Susan Mehringer 10/98, 1998; V-1376 (Box 9)
  - Lucy Walle 7/00, 2000; V-1376 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg 10/20/00 Multimatlas, 2000; V-1377 (Box 9)
  - Jarek Pillardy 22.19-26'00 Bioinformatics, 2000; V-1377 (Box 9)
  - MPI Collective Communication 1, Dan Dwyer 10-98, 1998; V-1378 (Box 9)
  - MPI Basics Dan Dwyer, 1998; V-1379 (Box 9)
  - MPI Coll Comm II Steve Lantz, 1998; V-1379 (Box 9)
  - MPI Point-to-Point Communication 1 Susan Mehringer 10/98, 1998; V-1380 (Box 9)
  - Lifka camera 1 10-15-01, 2001; V-1381 (Box 9)
  - Lifka camera 2 10-15-01, 2001; V-1382 (Box 9)
  - Machine Room B-Roll 12-04-01, 2001; V-1383 (Box 9)
  - Mansfield, Talking Head etc., Manhattan Lecture, 2001; V-1384 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 1: Honig, 2000; V-1385 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 2: Yona, 2000; V-1386 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 3: Stephen Harvey, 2000; V-1387 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 4: Tamar Schlick, 2000; V-1388 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 5: David Shmoys (Cornell), 2000; V-1389 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 6: David Shalloway (Cornell), 2000; V-1390 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 7: Eugene Shakhndvich (Harvard), 2000; V-1391 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 1 - 8: Harold Scheraga (Cornell), 2000; V-1392 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 1: Lasmus Nielsen (Cornell), 2000; V-1393 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 2: John Straub (Boston U), 2000; V-1394 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 3: Ron Elber (Cornell), 2000; V-1395 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 4: Jarek Meller (Cornell), 2000; V-1396 (Box 9)